referralblast.com 2010-05-27

# Referral Blast Website Promotion and Marketing

**Referral Blast Privacy Policy**

| [](http://clicktoverify.truste.com/pvr.php?page=validate&url=www.referralblast.com&sealid=101) | By participating in the TRUSTe Privacy Program and the Council of Better Business Bureau's BBBOnLine Reliability Program, Referral Blast has made a commitment to meet the programs' strict requirements regarding how we treat your information. Further information about these programs is available at http://www.truste.com and http://www.bbbonline.org.  
---|---  
  
We know that you care how information about you and your website visitors is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly.

This notice describes our privacy policy:

**Is personal information about my website visitors or the people they refer publicly used by Referral Blast in any way?**

No. When a visitor clicks on your Referral Blast button or text link, a smaller window opens allowing the visitor to enter their name (optional), up to 10 email addresses of people they want to tell about the site and a custom message (optional). Referral Blast never records or 'harvests' this information for spam or public purposes, nor sells it to third-parties. We do not spam and do not associate ourselves with organizations that support such activity. Referral Blast derives its revenue solely from the sale of its product and service offerings. We understand that our success is dependent upon the success of our clients, and that the trust of our clients and their visitors is one of our most important assets to be protected at all times. This collected third party personal information is used exclusively for the purpose of providing the service of sending this one time email and is stored exclusively for the purpose of measuring the effectiveness of our services.

**Information Collection & Use**

_Registration_

In order to signup for our service, you must first complete the order form and create a password. During registration you are required to give contact information such as your name and email address so that we may process your order and contact you about the service in which you have expressed interest. Upon registration, you will receive an order confirmation by email as well as required setup information for the level of service you requested. Referral Blast Website Promotion, LLC is the sole owner of the registration information collected on ReferralBlast.com. Referral Blast Website Promotion, LLC collects personally identifiable information from our users at several different points on our Web site.

_Orders_

If you purchase a product or service from us, we request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order form. You must provide contact information (such as name, billing address and email address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date). We use this information for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you. Upon completing your order, you will receive an order confirmation by email as well as required setup information for the level of service you requested.

_Surveys or Contests_

From time-to-time we may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys on our site. If you participate, we will request certain personally identifiable information (name, email address) from you. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information.

_Tell-A-Friend_

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. Referral Blast Website Promotion, LLC will only store this information if we are running a promotion or contest so that we may notify you if you are a winner. Otherwise, this information is not used for any other purpose than to send the one-time email. During any sort of promotion or contest you or your friend may contact us here to request that we remove this information from our database.

_Agents_

We use a credit card processing company to bill you for any services ordered. This company does not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any other purpose.

_Service Providers_

We use PayPal as an alternate billing option for order fulfillment on our site. When you sign up for any of our services using PayPal, you are redirected to PayPal's web site in order to complete your transaction. PayPal is prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for any other purpose.

_Information Sharing_

Referral Blast Website Promotion, LLC does not share, sell, rent, or trade your personally identifiable information with third parties for their promotional purposes.

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.

**Communications from the Site**

_Service-related Announcements_

We will send you service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email. Generally, you may not opt-out of this communication, which is not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive it, you have the option to deactivate your account. To de-activate your account, contact us using our 'Contact Us' form, call 732-923-0440 Monday through Friday between the hours of 9:30am and 5:30pm EST, or write us at Referral Blast, 1175 Lincoln Square, PO Box 2254, Long Branch, NJ 07740-2254. Your account will be de-activated within 72 hours of your request.

_Usage Notifications_

You may choose to receive an email notification that informs you when your service is used. This will only occur if you enable this option and you may opt-out from this email notification service at any time via your account's Control Panel.

_Customer Service_

Based upon the personally identifiable information you provide us, we will send you a welcoming email to verify your username and password. We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account. We will communicate with you by email or telephone, in accordance with your wishes.

**How is the personal information I provide for credit card processing used?**

During the order process, personal information such as your name, billing address, and credit card information is requested. This information is used strictly to process your order or to contact you with regard to the product. It is in no way disclosed, distributed or sold to third parties for their promotional purposes, or otherwise beyond our service providers as described above.

**Access to Personally Identifiable Information**

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may update your information, or delete/deactivate your account by making the change in your member Control Panel or contacting us using our contact form, or calling 732-923-0440 Monday through Friday between the hours of 9:30am and 5:30pm EST, or writing us at Referral Blast, PO Box 2254, Long Branch, NJ 07740-2254.

**Security**

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number on our registration/order form) we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us here.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close you browser. We do not use persistent cookies (a persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time). If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site, such as contests or surveys, will be limited. For more information about cookies, please visit <http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Web_browser_cookie>. Some of our business partners use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies. . We may from time to time employ the use of a third party agent in tracking aggregated non-personal statistical data about our site’s user base. This third party employs the use of cookies and web beacons (a one pixel image embedded within a web page) to this end. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by Referral Blast only and does not cover the use of cookies by our business partners whose cookies we have no access to, or responsibility for.

**Testimonials**

Testimonials at the site are submitted voluntarily by Referral Blast customers and only with their permission. Referral Blast customers can choose whether or not to have their Personally Identifiable Information published along with their testimonials. Referral Blast is not responsible for the personal information a customer elects to publish within their testimonial, nor for any unsolicited messages they may receive as a result.

**Contacting Us**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, Referral Blast's information practices, or your dealings with Referral Blast, you can contact us using our 'Contact Us' form, call 732-923-0440 Monday through Friday between the hours of 9:30am and 5:30pm EST, or write us at Referral Blast, 1175 Lincoln Square, PO Box 2254, Long Branch, NJ 07740-2254.

**Changes in this Privacy Statement**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.

**TRUSTe Privacy Program**

Referral Blast Website Promotion, LLC is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. TRUSTe is an independent organization whose mission is to build user's trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. This privacy statement covers the Web site http://www.referralblast.com. Because this Web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe. If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact Juliana Leschinsky at 732-923-0440 or via our feedback form. If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry within a reasonable time frame, or your inquiry hasn’t been addressed to your satisfaction please contact [TRUSTe](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint&url=) who shall then work as a liaison in assisting us to resolve your concerns.

**Last updated on October 13, 2009**
